[Audience cheering]
[观众欢呼]
And right now... Right now...
而现在...眼下...
Right now it's time to...
眼下，它的时间...
Kick out the jams, motherfucker!
揪出来的果酱，狗娘养的！
[Mc5's kick out the jams]
[卡纸MC5开出任意球]
♪ Yeah
♪呀
♪ I--I--I I'm gonna
♪我 - 我 - 我，我要去
♪ I'm gonna kick out--
♪我会踢出 -
[record scrapes, music stops]
[记录擦伤，音乐停了下来]
[Music, high-pitching whining]
[音乐，高投球呜呜]
♪
Dude, come on, man.
老兄，拜托，老兄。
Take this horrible shit off.
把这个可怕狗屎。
What the hell? I'm listening to that.
到底是什么？我听。
If mom comes home, she'll make me shut it off.
如果妈妈回家时，她会让我把它关掉。
All right, well, I'm doing her a favor then.
好，好，我做她的青睐。
[High pitched whining, screaming resumes]
[高刺耳尖叫简历]
Dude, you know what?
老兄，你知道吗？
This is really, like, making me crazy.
这是真的一样，让我疯了。
Then leave.
然后离开。
What? I just got here.
什么？我刚来到这里。
What are you doing, by the way?
你在做什么，顺便说一下吗？
I'm starting a magazine.
我开始一本杂志。
Like... like "nineteen" instead of sixteen?
喜欢...喜欢“19”，而不是16吗？
Or "twenty-one"?
或“二十一”？
Or, no, no, no, wait.
或者，不，不，不，等等。
We should totally go younger-- thirteen.
我们完全应该去年轻 -  13。
Get in on the newbie chicks.
获取新手雏鸡。
No. It's a magazine for fuck-up kids.
这是他妈的孩子一本杂志。
Like kids who have parties
像有各方的孩子谁
when their parents are away and destroy the house.
当他们的父母离开，毁坏房子。
Cool! I could be, like, the editor or something.
爽！我可以，喜欢的编辑器或东西。
No. I'm the editor and the illustrator.
我编辑和插画。
Well, what does that leave me?
那么，究竟是什么离开我吗？
You're just a punk.
你只是一个朋克。
Guess I am just a punk.
猜猜我只是一个朋克。
"Punk." That's a great title.
“朋克”。这是一个伟大的冠军。
Yeah. That was my idea, dude. I thought of that idea.
嗯。这是我的主意，伙计。我想到了这个主意。
What? No, you didn't.
什么？不，你没有。
I just said, "that's a great title."
我只是说，“这是一个伟大的冠军。”
Who gave you the idea for "punk"?
谁给你的“朋克”的想法吗？
Who said it was a great title?
谁说过这是一个伟大的冠军？
[Talking heads' life during wartime]
[谈元首的战时生活]
♪
♪ Heard of a van
♪听说一辆面包车
♪ it's loaded with weapons
♪装有武器
♪ packed up and ready to go ♪
♪收拾行装，准备去♪
♪ Heard of some grave sites
♪听说一些墓地
♪ out by the highway
♪由高速公路
♪ a place where nobody knows ♪
♪没有人知道的地方♪
♪ The sound of gunfire
♪枪声
♪ off in the distance
♪在距离
♪ I'm getting used to it now ♪
♪我习惯现在♪
♪ Lived in a brownstone
♪住在赤褐色砂石建筑
♪ lived in a ghetto
♪住在贫民窟
♪ I've lived all over this town ♪
♪我住在这个小镇♪
♪ This ain't no party
♪这不是任何一方
♪ this ain't no disco
♪这不是没有迪斯科
♪ this ain't no fooling around ♪
♪♪左右，这不是没有嘴硬
♪ This ain't no mudd club
♪这不是没有穆德俱乐部
♪ or CBGB
♪或CBGB
♪ I ain't got time for that now ♪
♪我是不是得了时间，现在♪
♪
♪ Heard about Houston
♪听说关于休斯敦
♪ heard about Detroit...
♪听说底特律...
[Music box playing]
[音乐盒播放]
♪
[Crying]
[哭]
Ow!
嗷！
[Rock music]
[摇滚音乐]
♪
[Cow moos]
[牛穆斯]
[Woman screams]
[女人的尖叫声]
Hillel, where are you?
希勒尔，你在哪里？
Hillel?! Hilly!
希勒尔？希利！
Kidnapped?
绑架？
Bertha, no one kidnaps from the poor.
伯莎从穷人，没有人绑架。
What? Hilly's missing.
什么？希利失踪。
Get your truck.
让您的卡车。
Go, go, go! Run!
走，走，走！快跑！
[Brakes squeal]
[刹车尖叫]
How did he get here?
他怎么在这里？
He must've walked?
他意有所指走？
Three Miles?
三英里？
It's two and a half.
这是两年半。
That's not normal.
这是不正常的。
[Man] Hillel Kristal.
[文]希勒尔克里什塔尔。
You currently reside at 21 east 2nd street?
您目前位于东二街21？
And what is your marital status, Mr. Kristal?
什么是你的婚姻状况，克里什塔尔先生？
My wife and I are split.
我的妻子和分裂。
Separated or divorced?
分居或离婚？
Divorced. Yep.
离婚。没错。
Children?
孩子？
Two.
二。
And this is your... second failed attempt to run a bar.
这是你的......第二次失败的尝试运行吧。
A club.
一个俱乐部。
Divorced and two bankruptcies.
离婚和两个破产。
Perhaps you should try something else.
也许你应该尝试别的东西。
♪ I'm sick of the parties
♪我生病各方
♪ I'm sick of the ravers
♪我生病的舞客
♪ I'm sick of the dogs and my noisy neighbors ♪
♪我生病的狗和我吵闹的邻居♪
♪ I'm sick of the subways and I'm sick of the crowds ♪
♪我生病的地铁，我生病的人群♪
♪ I'm sick of hot water always running out ♪
♪我生病的热水始终运行♪
♪ I'm sick of the crap I gotta take in this town ♪
♪我生病的废话我要在这个小镇♪
♪ If I didn't love it
♪如果我不喜欢它
♪ I swear I'd burn it to the ground ♪
♪我发誓，我将它刻录到地面♪
♪ I'm sick of the tourists
♪我生病的游客
♪ I'm sick of their stares
♪我生病了他们的凝视
♪ I'm sick of all the girls
♪我所有的女孩生病
♪ who ain't showin' their wares ♪
♪谁不舒'他们的产品♪
♪ I'm sick of the queens and I'm sick of the whores ♪
♪我生病的皇后，我生病的妓女♪
♪ I'm sick of bad lovin' and those raconteurs ♪
♪我生病坏的lovin'和那些RACONTEURS，♪
♪ I'm sick of the crap I gotta take in this town ♪
♪我生病的废话我要在这个小镇♪
♪ I'm sick
♪我生病
♪ if I didn't love it
♪如果我不喜欢它
♪ I swear I'd burn it to the ground ♪
♪我发誓，我将它刻录到地面♪
♪ You know I'm sick
♪你知道我生病了
♪ if I didn't love it
♪如果我不喜欢它
♪ I swear I'd burn it to the ground ♪
♪我发誓，我将它刻录到地面♪
♪ I'm sick of the crap I gotta take in this town ♪
♪我生病的废话我要在这个小镇♪
♪ I'm really sick
♪我真的病
you play?
你玩吗？
Used to.
习惯了。
Me too.
我也一样。
Mother required it.
母亲需要。
Hilly Kristal.
希利克里什塔尔。
They call me Idaho.
他们叫我爱达荷州。
Why's that?
为什么？
I like potatoes.
我喜欢土豆。
[Scoffs]
[嘲笑]
Buy you a drink?
请你喝一杯吗？
The palace bar.
宫殿吧。
I like the irony.
我喜欢讽刺。
What'll you have?
你要什么东西？
Whiskey.
威士忌。
Brandy and Fresca.
白兰地和弗雷斯卡。
No Fresca.
没有弗雷斯卡。
Soda.
苏打水。
Anyone play music in here?
在这里的人播放音乐？
No.
不
Nobody'd complain about the noise this far downtown.
没人会抱怨噪音这么远的市中心。
They'd complain, but no one would listen.
他们会抱怨，但没有人会听。
Think what a coat of paint could do.
想想粉刷可以做什么。
Or a bulldozer.
还是一台推土机。
I wanna buy this bar.
我想要买这个吧。
Got any money?
带钱？
[The velvet underground's heroin]
[地下丝绒的海洛因]
♪
[Clock ticking]
[时钟滴答]
Look around, hillel.
环顾四周，希勒尔。
You know that I'm not made of money.
你知道，我不发钱。
This rugelach looks amazing, Mrs. Kristal.
此俄式肉桂酥卷看起来惊人，夫人克里什塔尔。
Oh, you're such a good boy, Merv.
哦，你是个好孩子，梅尔夫。
Take some more.
采取更多一些。
Merv, are you gonna be working with, uh, hillel
梅尔夫，你要去工作，呃，希勒尔
on the new club?
在新的俱乐部？
Only if he pays me.
只有当他付给我。
He'll pay you.
他会付钱给你。
Am I correct, hillel?
我纠正，希勒尔？
♪ All the boys, they're putting me down... ♪
♪所有的男孩，他们把我下来...... ♪
♪ I know what they say when I ain't around ♪
♪我知道他们在说什么，当我不在你身边♪
♪ He can't make it...
♪他不能让...
Can't play with broken strings, Idaho.
断了的弦不能玩，爱达荷。
Thanks, hilly.
谢谢，希利。
Hilly's on the bowery.
希利上的包厘街。
Very nice.
很不错的。
Another promising investment opportunity for your mother.
另一种有前途的投资机会，为您的母亲。
This way to the kitchen.
通过这种方式来厨房。
And lose that phony accent, Merv.
而失去，假口音，梅尔夫。
Two more blasts of ketchup.
两个爆炸番茄酱。
How many is that so far?
是，到目前为止有多少呢？
Uh, fifteen.
嗯，15。
It's a trainwreck.
这是一个肉肉又多多。
What a surprise. Nice to see you too.
什么一个惊喜。很高兴见到你。
I'm dropping out of school, dad. Well, you shouldn't.
我辍学，爸爸。好吧，你不应该。
Well, I can't afford it.
好吧，我买不起它。
So that's my fault? Yeah.
所以这是我的错吗？嗯。
Look, I need a place to crash.
你看，我需要一个地方坠毁。
Just for a couple of nights
只为一对夫妇晚
until I get things back on track.
得到的东西，直到我回到正轨。
You leave that boyfriend yet?
你离开那个男朋友吗？
You consider getting a real job yet?
你认为得到一份真正的工作吗？
[Rock music]
[摇滚音乐]
♪
Well, it's a start.
嗯，这是一个开始。
We have a stage.
我们有一个阶段。
Now we need an income.
现在，我们需要收入。
I was thinking 50 cent beers and topless waitresses
我在想，50美分的啤酒和赤裸上身的女服务员
like that joint down on...
这样的联合羽绒...
Look, the music'll do it all for us.
你看，音乐为我们做这一切。
You start playing that disco shit, I'm gone.
你开始玩，迪斯科狗屎，我走了。
Country and blues.
国家和蓝调。
In New York City?
在纽约市？
This club's gonna be different.
这个俱乐部会有所不同。
Country and blues.
国家和蓝调。
Country, bluegrass, blues.
国家，兰草，蓝调。
I shoulda never left my other job.
我早该从来没有离开过我的其他工作。
The place was a shit hole.
那地方是一片屎坑。
This place is a shit hole.
这个地方是一个屎坑。
Idaho, come on.
爱达荷州，来吧。
I'm locking up.
我锁定了。
It's the only bar in the city with Fresca on tap.
这是唯一的酒吧弗雷斯卡在城市自来水。
Yeah, but that shit'll kill ya.
是啊，但是那傻逼会杀了你。
[Rock music]
[摇滚音乐]
♪
Uh, hello!
呃，你好！
We hear you have a stage.
我们听说你有一个阶段。
We have a band.
我们有一个乐队。
The perfect band to perform on your stage.
完美的乐队，舞台上的表演。
What kind of music do you play?
你喜欢玩什么样的音乐呢？
Uh, new music.
嗯，新的音乐。
Uh, what does "CBGB" stand for?
呃，“CBGB”的立场是什么？
Country, bluegrass, blues.
国家，兰草，蓝调。
They play a little of that.
他们玩一点点。
A little rock, a little country,
小石城，一个小国，
a little bluegrass, a little blues.
一点点的兰草，一点点蓝色。
Hey, didn't you used to manage the village vanguard?
嘿，你没有用于管理先锋村？
Hundred years ago.
一百多年前。
One moment.
一个时刻。
Get a load of him.
他的负荷。
[Country music playing]
[乡村音乐播放]
Terry Ork. I manage the band television.
特里 欧科。我是乐队television的经理人。
Oh.
哦。
Uh, you just met the guitar players, Richard and tom, outside.
呃，你刚刚认识的吉他手，理查德和汤姆，外面。
It's a win-win.
这是一个双赢。
CBGB gets new customers buying drinks
CBGB获取新客户购买饮料
and we get to play for an audience.
我们可以玩一个观众。
They any good?
他们有什么好处？
They are... raw, man!
他们是...原材料，伙计！
They're primitive.
他们是原始的。
They are going to be huge.
他们都将是巨大的。
I bet they stink.
我敢打赌，他们很臭。
But maybe if they perform...
但也许，如果他们的表现...
They'll get better.
他们会变得更好。
All right.
好的。
You've got some vision, man.
你已经得到了一定的眼光，男人。
Only original music.
只有原创音乐。
You got it.
你得到了它。
Ah, that way you get to avoid paying ASCAP fees.
啊，这样，你得到避免支付ASCAP费。
It's a philosophy.
这是一个理念。
You might wanna consider an exterminator.
您可能要考虑灭虫。
Just...
只是......
You got a good sound engineer?
你有一个很好的录音师？
You're talking to a man who sang at radio city.
你说一个人在无线电城谁唱的。
[The stooges' 1969]
[走狗“1969年]
♪
♪ Oh my and a--a boo hoo
♪哦，我和一个 - 嘘呼
hilly Kristal.
希利克里什塔尔。
My hands are dirty, okay?
我的手脏了，好吗？
What's your name?
你叫什么名字？
Taxi.
出租车。
I'm not much of a dog person.
我没有太多的狗的人。
But you're mechanical.
但你机械。
You musical?
你的音乐吗？
Yeah, I played in a band once.
是啊，我曾经在一个乐队演奏。
My guitar was stolen.
我的吉他被偷走。
I have a position at my club.
我有一个在我的俱乐部的地位。
Are you paying?
你付出吗？
Yes.
是。
♪ Oh my and a--a boo hoo
♪哦，我和一个 - 嘘呼
hey, what-- how do I--?
哎，什么 - 我该怎么办 - ？
Shit.
妈的。
This is taxi.
这是出租车。
My sound engineer.
我的录音师。
Hey, man.
嘿，伙计。
You're gonna wanna crank it.
你要去想曲柄。
You play too loud, I'm walking out.
你玩太大，我走了。
Hey, whenever you're ready!
嘿，只要你准备好了！
♪ You know I I jump outta bed ♪
♪你知道我跳下床♪
♪ I pull down the shade
♪我拉下遮阳
♪ I used to have such sweet dreams ♪
♪我曾经有过这样甜蜜的梦♪
♪ Now it's more like an air raid ♪
♪现在它更像空袭♪
♪ I see the opposition clear
♪我清楚看到反对派
♪ I see them glare
♪我看到他们怒目而视
♪ I don't care
♪我不在乎
♪ it doesn't matter to me
♪不要紧我
♪ I don't care
♪我不在乎
♪ I never think about it
♪我从来没有想过它
♪ I don't care
♪我不在乎
♪ slip out of myself like a shadow ♪
♪滑出自己像一个影子♪
Second verse is a lot better.
第二首诗是好了很多。
♪ And somersault through walls ♪
♪翻腾穿过墙壁♪
♪ I can't tell, it's really so odd ♪
♪我不能告诉，这是真的有这么奇怪♪
♪ Is it spring or fall?
♪是春季或秋季？
I thought it was good.
我想这是很好的。
Not very country.
不是很国家。
Going to have to change that name.
去必须改变名称。
False advertising.
虚假广告。
What do you think?
你觉得呢？
"I don't care.
“我不在乎。
"It doesn't matter to me.
“不要紧，我。
"I don't care.
“我不在乎。
"I never think about it.
“我从来没有去想它。
I don't care."
我不在乎。“
There's something there.
那里有什么东西。
I can see it. There is something there.
我可以看到它。有那么点意思。
[Stomach gurgling]
[胃潺潺]
Jonathan, your stomach's growling.
乔纳森，你的肚子咕咕叫。
Do you wanna go get a bagel?
你想和我去一个面包圈？
Lisa, you want something to eat?
丽莎，你想吃点什么？
No.
号
I ate your chili last night.
我吃你辣椒昨晚。
So...
所以......
If you're not going to school,
如果你不上学，
are you getting a job?
你得到一份工作吗？
It's 7:30 in the morning.
这是在早晨7:30。
You gotta have some plan. What is it?
你得有一些计划。这是什么？
To not be here when you get back.
不会在这里，你回来的时候。
Ugh. Shit!
唉。妈的！
[Richard hell and the Voidoids' blank generation]
[Richard hell and the Voidoids'的空白代]
♪ I was saying let me out of here ♪
♪我说让我离开这里♪
♪ Before I was even born
♪之前，我还没有出生
♪ it's such a gamble when you get a face ♪
♪它是这样一场赌博，当你得到一个脸♪
♪ It's fascinating to observe what the mirror does ♪
♪这是迷人的观察镜子♪
♪ But when I dine it's for the wall that I set a place ♪
♪不过我吃饭的时候，它的墙，我设置了一个地方♪
♪ I belong to the blank generation and ♪
♪我属于空白代♪
♪ I can take it or leave it each time ♪
♪我可以接受，要么离开它每次♪
'Scuse me. I have to open up.
“打扰一下。我有去开拓。
He's dead.
他死了。
I've been watchin' him for you, hilly.
我一直看着他，希利。
Has anybody informed the police?
有没有人通知警方？
Nah. Cops don't care too much
罗。警察不要太在意
about dead guys in the bowery.
在包厘街的死家伙。
Where'd he come from?
他来自哪儿？
Upstairs.
楼上的。
[Telephone ringing]
[电话铃声]
[Man] Somebody answer that?
[文]有人的答案是什么？
Hey, answer the phone already!
嘿，接电话了！
There's a dead body outside.
有一个尸体外。
You wanna come see if it's one of your guests?
你想过来看看，如果它是一个你的客人？
Not particularly.
没有什么特别的。
Had a guy stabbed in the shower here last month.
有一个家伙在这里的淋浴间刺伤上个月。
Big mess. Had to call the cops three times.
大烂摊子。只好叫警察三次。
Pain in my ass.
疼痛在我的屁股。
What? You want a room?
什么？你想要一个房间吗？
What's going on, Stan?
这是怎么回事，斯坦？
I'm arresting this man under suspicion of murder.
我下逮捕了这名男子因涉嫌故意杀人。
Whose suspicion?
谁的怀疑呢？
Look, Kristal. Let me do my job, okay?
看，克里什塔尔。让我做我的工作，好吗？
What about the body?
身体怎么样？
Welcome to CBGB, gentlemen.
欢迎CBGB，先生们。
Compliments of the house.
鸣谢的房子。
And who the hell are you?
和你到底是谁？
Hilly Kristal.
希利克里什塔尔。
Police took a guy for murder today.
警方采取了谋杀家伙今天。
Yeah, we heard.
是啊，我们听到了。
He didn't do it.
他没有做到这一点。
Plays the violin.
播放小提琴。
We call him Idaho.
我们叫他爱达荷州。
Yeah, he's a little guy.
是啊，他是一个小家伙。
Yeah. He's that junkie.
嗯。他迷。
I'd like to help him,
我想帮他，
but I need
但我需要
some guidance on that.
一些指导。
What do we get out of it?
我们得到什么呢？
I'm your neighbor.
我是你的邻居。
Got lots of neighbors.
有很多邻居。
You treat me right,
你把我的权利，
I'll treat you right.
我会好好对待你。
I'll make a call.
我会拨打电话。
Merv!
梅尔夫！
Another round of beers for our neighbors here.
另一轮的啤酒，我们这里的邻居。
Hey, hilly.
嘿，希利。
Hello, Idaho.
你好，爱达荷。
I'm sorry about this.
我很抱歉。
[Groans] Jail's not so bad.
[呻吟]监狱不是那么糟糕。
At least they got heat.
至少他们得到的热量。
[The velvet underground's I can't stand it]
[地下丝绒的我无法忍受]
♪
Why'd you come?
你为什么要来？
'Cause you needed me to.
因为你需要我。
You read much?
你看了多少？
I'm a junkie, hilly.
我是一个迷，希利。
Do I look like I read fucking books to you?
你看我像我读你他妈的书？
"Small is beautiful:
“小是美丽的：
A study of economics as if people mattered."
经济学的研究，如果人们重要的。“
Just came out.
刚出来的时候。
Talks about how economics
谈经济如何
has become the dominant ideological force in society.
已成为在社会占主导地位的思想力。
How we need to re-think that.
我们需要重新思考，如何。
With art. Music.
与艺术。音乐。
You're out of gas.
你出来的气体。
It's only a few more blocks.
这是只多块。
He's got vodka?
他有伏特加？
♪ I can't stand it anymore--more ♪
♪我不能忍受下去了 - ♪
♪ I can't stand it anymore--ore ♪
♪我不能忍受它了 - 矿石♪
♪ I can't stand it anymore--more ♪
♪我不能忍受下去了 - ♪
[Engine starts]
[引擎启动]
♪
♪ I remember
♪我记得
♪ ooh how the darkness doubled ♪
♪嚯如何黑暗一倍♪
♪ I recall
♪我记得
♪ lightning struck itself ♪
♪雷电击中♪
♪ I was listening
♪我在听
♪ listening to the rain
♪听雨
oh, shit.
哦，狗屎。
That's not good.
这是不好的。
Damn shower.
该死的淋浴。
This place is... Cool, man.
这个地方是...酷男人。
I told you not to...
我告诉你，不...
Hey! Hey! 2.50!
嘿！嘿！ 2.50！
Aw, Jesus!
噢，耶！
Hey! You're blocking the drain!
嘿！你堵漏！
Good working with you.
良好的工作与你同在。
Yeah. I'll see you tomorrow?
嗯。明天我会看到你吗？
Yes.
是。
Seven dollars? How am I supposed to live on this?
七美元？我应该住在这吗？
Hey, man. Art sucks.
嘿，伙计。艺术很烂。
Not a bad night.
不是一个糟糕的夜晚。
Nearly electrocuted a guy.
近触电的一个家伙。
Doubled the attendance.
出席了一倍。
[Rock music]
[摇滚音乐]
♪
"OMFUG?"
“OMFUG？”
Other music for uplifting...
令人振奋的其他音乐...
Gormandizers.
老饕。
Oh, yeah. Well, that explains it.
哦，是的。嗯，这说明它。
Your mother called.
你妈妈叫。
She wants to know when you're paying her back.
她想知道，当你付出她的背部。
Did you tell her we need a little time?
你告诉她，我们需要一点时间吗？
I did.
我做到了。
And that things are picking up.
而且，事情正在加快。
So what's the problem? I lied.
那么，有什么问题吗？我撒了谎。
I am working on some other
我的工作在其他一些
financial opportunities.
金融机会。
Excellent.
优秀的。
Watch it!
当心！
You book any country yet?
你预订任何国家？
Closest I got was some guy named Wayne county
最近我得到的是一些家伙叫韦恩县
who's thinking of becoming a jayne county.
谁的思想成为杰恩县的。
I was hearing "country," he was saying "county."
我所听到的“国家”，他说：“县。”
Thank you. Thank you very much.
谢谢。非常感谢。
Good day.
今天好。
Thank you.
谢谢。
[Groans]
[呻吟]
W-w-w-wait.
W-W-W-稍候。
I gotta pee.
我要撒尿。
Hold it! I can't!
hold不住了！我不能！
You are not going!
你不去！
I'll be back.
我会回来的。
Aah!
啊哈！
Maybe it was a mistake to hire a junkie as the third hand.
也许这是一个错误，聘请了迷第三只手。
Hurry up!
快点！
Excellent.
优秀的。
So much for the lucrative world of piano delivery.
这么多的利润丰厚的世界钢琴交付。
See? I was quick!
看到了吗？我快！
Uh-oh.
嗯，哦。
[Nixon] In all of my years of public life
[尼克松]我多年的公共生活
I have never profited--
我从来没有获利 -
never profited from public service.
从来没有从中获利的公共服务。
I have never obstructed justice.
我从来没有阻挠司法公正。
Because people have gotta know
因为人们已经知道
whether or not their president is a crook.
不论他们的总统是骗子。
Well, I'm not a crook.
好吧，我不是一个骗子。
I've earned everything I've got--
我已经赢得了一切，我有 -
[man] All right.
[男人]的所有权利。
Right there. No way, man.
就在那里。没办法，男人。
[Laughter]
[笑]
If you guys weren't neighbors,
如果你们是不是邻居，
I'd put that chair on your bill, Bert.
我把那把椅子，在您的账单，伯特。
Bert fuck you, hilly.
伯特你他妈的，希利。
This table, it tilts.
这个表，它倾斜。
They shorted us on the hard liquor order.
他们短路烈性酒顺序。
If we don't pay the bill, they'll cut us off.
如果我们不支付账单，他们就砍我们。
Lisa. Hi.
丽莎。嗨。
You leaving that rotten boyfriend
你离开那个烂男友
and going back to school?
回去上学吗？
No.
号
If it's money you came for--
如果这是钱，你来了 -
you seen this?
你见过这个吗？
No.
号
"The great thing about this band, television,
“伟大的事情对这个乐队，电视，
"is that they have absolutely no musical
“他们绝对没有音乐
"or socially redeeming characteristics
“或社会赎回特性
and they know it."
他们知道这一点。“
Who wrote that? Josh Feigenbaum.
是谁写的？乔希·费根鲍姆。
Who's he? He's important.
他是谁？他最重要的。
So people are gonna read this
所以人们会阅读本
and they're gonna start talking.
他们会开始谈论。
And bands are gonna start showing up wanting to play here.
和乐队都会开始显示想在这里打球。
And all bands have fans, even the shitty ones.
所有波段的球迷，甚至是低劣的。
And everybody wants to be in a band and have fans,
每个人都希望在一个乐队，并配有风扇，
so new bands are gonna start up and show up.
那么新的乐队会启动并显示出来。
You have no idea what's about to happen here.
你根本不知道什么是即将在这里发生。
So...
所以......
Gimme a job.
给我一份工作。
The pay sucks.
薪酬吮吸。
The music sucks.
音乐很烂。
But far be it from me
但到目前为止它从我
to refute the words of Josh Feigenbaum.
乔希·费根鲍姆的话来反驳。
What do you expect to do around here?
你希望在这里做什么？
Well, what do you do around here?
那么，你在这里做什么？
Do you want a job, or do you want to fight?
你想要一份工作，或者你想打架吗？
I asked you for a job.
我问你找工作。
Fine.
精细。
Okay.
好吧。
To start with,
首先，
bands will sound-check from 4:00 to 6:00.
乐队听起来会检查从4:00到6:00。
Yeah.
嗯。
I'll post the lineup at 7:30.
我会在7:30发布的阵容。
And bands don't get to decide the order.
带不来决定顺序。
They fight, they're out. Got it.
他们打了，他们没有。得到它。
Anything else?
还有别的吗？
Yeah. Bikers don't pay for their drinks.
嗯。骑自行车的人不支付他们的饮料。
When? A lot.
什么时候？很多。
Ever. Why not?
如初。为什么不呢？
Policy.
政策。
CBGB.
CBGB。
Collection services. Hilly Kristal?
收集服务。希利克里什塔尔？
Hold on. Bill collectors.
保持。比尔收藏家。
You're hired.
你录用。
Clean up on aisle 10.
清理过道10。
Oh, he is not talking to me, is he?
哦，他是不是在跟我说话，是他？
Yes. He is.
是。他是。
Uh, fourteen.
嗯，14。
Thirteen.
十三。
[Coughs]
[咳嗽]
Eleven.
十一。
Twelve.
十二个​​。
Idaho. Hey. Where's the beer?
爱达荷州。嘿。啤酒在哪里？
There's no beer. What do you mean?
有没有啤酒。你是什​​么意思？
Hilly didn't pay the bill.
希利没有埋单。
Same reason there's no phone.
同样的原因，也没有电话。
We don't need a phone. We have a payphone.
我们并不需要一个电话。我们有一个公用电话。
We're a bar. We need beer!
我们是一个酒吧。我们需要的啤酒！
Jesus Christ. Look at this!
耶稣基督。看看这个！
Will you--? Look at the size of that rat.
请问您 - ？看，老鼠的大小。
Don't point at him. Why?
不要指向他。为什么呢？
It upsets him. Who?
这让他烦恼。是谁？
Bert.
伯特。
Bert. Bert the rat?
伯特。伯特的老鼠？
We have a deal.
我们有一个协议。
What are you talking about?
你说的是什么？
He doesn't bite me if I feed him.
他不咬我，如果我喂他。
Hilly spent a fortune on exterminating cockroaches
希利花了财富消灭蟑螂
and you're feeding the fucking rats?
你喂养的他妈的大鼠？
Shh!
嘘！
He's listening.
他在听。
You're gonna make him mad!
你会是他疯了！
How's the chili? Bert likes it.
辣椒如何？伯特喜欢它。
If Bert doesn't eat it,
如果伯特不会吃它，
I know can't feed it to anybody else.
我知道不能养活别人。
Well, as long as Bert likes it.
好吧，只要，伯特喜欢。
Get rid of Bert. Right now.
摆脱伯特麦。眼下。
And find some beer.
并找到了一些啤酒。
I like Lisa.
我喜欢丽莎。
I like Lisa a lot.
喜欢莉萨很多。
Hey! Here you go. Television.
嘿！在这里，你走。电视。
Check 'em out. Right around the corner.
检查'时间。在拐角处。
Here you go. Television.
在这里，你走。电视。
CBGB's.
CBGB的。
[Woman] I prefer the term underground rock.
[女人]我更喜欢长期的地下岩石。
"Underground" implies secretive.
“地下”意味着遮遮掩掩。
There's something precious about that to me.
有珍贵的东西给我。
Punk, on the other hand, it's in your face.
朋克，另一方面，它在你的脸上。
It's sarcastic, ironic, cutting.
这是讽刺，讽刺的是，切割。
So you're a punk.
所以你是一个朋克。
Yeah. I am too.
嗯。我也是一样。
I'm an illustrator, and I'm starting a magazine.
我是一名插画家，我开始一个杂志。
Yeah, it's called punk.
是啊，这就是所谓的朋克。
And your punk magazine
和你的朋克杂志
is going to hold forth the losers as winners.
为获奖者举行了失败者。
Deify the freaks and outcasts of the underground--
神化的怪胎和地下的弃儿 -
I mean downtown music scene.
我的意思是市中心乐坛。
Yes.
是。
Thou shalt keep no gods,
你要谨守不是神，
especially fossils like Eric Clapton and zeppelin.
尤其是埃里克·克莱普顿和飞艇等化石。
You wanna write for the magazine?
你想为杂志写？
What's a degree from Oxford for anyway?
从牛津反正是一个什么程度？
To impress your parents' friends.
为了你的父母的朋友留下深刻的印象。
I'm John. Mary.
我是约翰。玛丽。
Hey. Eddie Mcneil.
嘿。埃迪·麦克尼尔。
Hi, Eddie. Nice to meet ya.
嗨，埃迪。很高兴见到你。
A.K.A. "Legs."
亦称“腿”。
All right, legs.
所有权利，腿。
[Telephone rings]
[电话铃响]
CBGB.
CBGB。
[Man] Yeah, how late you open tonight? Until 4:00.
[文]是啊，你今晚打开多晚？直到4:00。
In the morning? A.M., right.
在早上呢？上午，右。
[Telephone rings]
[电话铃响]
CBGB.
CBGB。
Hey, you got that TV set band on tonight?
嘿，你得到的电视机带今晚？
Yes. Television.
是。电视。
David bowie says that television
大卫·鲍伊说，电视
is the most original band in New York.
是最原始的乐队在纽约。
[Telephone rings]
[电话铃响]
CBGB.
CBGB。
If that's what you want,
如果这是你想要什么，
I can take care of it for you.
我可以为你照顾好它。
Coming to you from the bowery of New York City...
你来纽约市的距离Bowery ...
Television!
电视！
♪ You know I I jump outta bed ♪
♪你知道我跳下床♪
♪ I pull down the shade
♪我拉下遮阳
♪ I used to have such sweet dreams ♪
♪我曾经有过这样甜蜜的梦♪
♪ Now it's more like an air raid ♪
♪现在它更像空袭♪
♪ I see the opposition clear ♪
♪我看到反对派明确♪
♪ I see them glare
♪我看到他们怒目而视
♪ I don't care
♪我不在乎
♪ it doesn't matter to me
♪不要紧我
♪ I don't care
♪我不在乎
♪ slip out of myself like a shadow ♪
♪滑出自己像一个影子♪
♪ Somersault through walls
♪穿墙空翻
♪ can't tell, it's really so odd ♪
♪不能告诉，这是真的有这么奇怪♪
♪ Is it spring or fall?
♪是春季或秋季？
I always thought a punk
我一直以为朋克
was someone who took it up the ass.
是有人谁把它的屁股。
They said they met at art school.
他们说，他们在艺术学校见面。
Looks like they sniffed some fumes
看起来他们嗅到一些烟雾
from all that paint and glue.
从所有的油漆和胶水。
Tell 'em to wait. Okay. Why?
告诉EM等待。好吧。为什么呢？
I'm going to see if I can increase the size of the house.
我要看看我是否能增加房子的大小。
Chief!
主管！
Just a minute.
只需一分钟。
We're gonna see if we can get more people to...
我们要看到，如果我们可以让更多的人......
Come in and listen to you.
来吧，听你的。
Okay?
好吗？
Stan, I'd like to invite you into the club
Stan，我想邀请你到俱乐部
to hear a band I think you will appreciate.
听到一个乐队，我想你会明白。
I'm working here, Kristal.
我在这里工作，蕊妮。
How about if I buy you a beer?
怎么样，如果我能给你买啤酒？
Look at that! Off duty.
瞧瞧吧！下班。
Two beers.
两个啤酒。
The name of this band is talking heads.
这个乐队的名字是名嘴。
We live across the street.
我们住在街对面。
♪
♪ I can't seem to face up to the facts ♪
♪我似乎无法面对的事实♪
♪ I'm tense and nervous and I can't relax ♪
♪我紧张和焦虑，我不能放松♪
♪ I can't sleep 'cause my bed's on fire ♪
♪♪我不能睡觉'引起我的床着火
♪ Don't touch me, I'm a real live wire ♪
♪不要碰我，我是一个真正的火线♪
♪ Psycho killer
♪心理杀手
♪ qu'est que c'est
♪qu'est雀仔
♪ fa fa fa fa fa fa fa fa fa fa ♪
♪发发发发发发发发发发♪
♪ Better run run run run
♪更好的运行运行运行运行
♪ run run run away
♪跑跑逃跑
♪ oh
♪哦
♪ psycho killer
♪变态杀手
♪ qu'est que c'est
♪qu'est雀仔
♪ fa fa fa fa fa fa fa fa fa fa ♪
♪发发发发发发发发发发♪
♪ Better run run run run
♪更好的运行运行运行运行
♪ run run run away
♪跑跑逃跑
♪ oh a-yi-yi-yi-yi!
♪哦一个义一义义！
Television.
电视。
The shirts. Orchestra luna.
衬衫。乐团LUNA。
The magic tramps. The fast.
魔法的流浪汉。快。
Tuff darts. Dorian zero.
凝灰岩飞镖。多利安为零。
The mumps. The miamis.
腮腺炎。热火队。
The planets. Leather secrets.
行星。皮革秘密。
Manster. The dictators.
Manster。独裁者。
Blondie.
金发女郎。
Blondie!
金发女郎！
You're so fuckin' hot.
你是如此“烫手。
You're gonna kill.
你会杀了。
You're gonna kill. Right.
你会杀了。右。
Stop it.
停止它。
All right, clem?
所有权利，克莱姆？
Hi. We're blondie.
嗨。我们是金发女郎。
You're gorgeous!
你华丽！
Thank you.
谢谢。
[Cheers and applause]
[欢呼和掌声]
You like my shorts?
你喜欢我的短裤吗？
New York has gorgeous garbage.
纽约有华丽的垃圾。
♪ Oh denis, ooh-be-doo
♪丹尼斯哦，哦斗
[man] Gotta get your ass down there!
[男人]总得让你的屁股！
Fuck!
他妈的！
Get your ass down there right now!
让你的屁股吧！
♪ I'm in love with you
♪我爱你
♪ denis ooh-be-doo
♪丹尼斯户外斗
♪ I'm in love with you
♪我爱你
bowery?
Bowery的？
I know there's stuff happening down there.
我知道有事情发生在那里。
It's just such a fuckin' shit hole.
这只是他妈的'屎坑。
♪ Oh, with your eyes so blue ♪
♪哦，用你的眼睛，所以蓝色♪
♪ Denis denis, I got a crush on you ♪
♪丹尼斯·丹尼斯，我迷恋你♪
♪ Denis denis, I'm so in love with you ♪
♪丹尼斯·丹尼斯，我是那么爱你♪
All right. All right. I'll go.
好的。好的。我会去的。
♪ Oh, when we walk
♪哦，当我们走
♪ it always feels so nice ♪
♪它总是感觉这么好♪
♪ And when we talk, it seems like... ♪
♪当我们说话的时候，好像...... ♪
Becky!
贝基！
[Becky] Yeah, Mr. Gant?
[贝基]是啊，甘特先生？
Becky, get me a...
贝基，给我一个...
Moist towelette.
湿巾。
♪ You're my king and I'm in heaven ♪
♪你是我的国王和我在天堂♪
♪ Every time I look at you ♪
♪每次我看着你♪
It's called a cover charge. All right.
这就是所谓的盖电荷。好的。
You gotta pay to enter. I don't have any money.
你必须付费才能进入。我没有什么钱。
Let 'em in, Lisa.
让'时间，丽莎。
Let 'em in.
让他们英寸
Thanks.
谢谢。
Fuck Max's.
他妈的最大的。
This place has dog shit.
这个地方有狗屎。
This is for all you drunks
这是所有醉鬼
and rednecks and punks.
和农场工人和小混混。
"As long as the blade has not yet pierced this brain,
“脑，只要叶片还没有无环
this fat and greenish package of listless vapors..."
这种脂肪和绿的包的无精打采蒸汽...“
[Audience groaning]
[观众呻吟]
Shut the fuck up!
闭嘴！
This is art. This is rimbaud.
这是艺术。这是兰波。
And it's the only sustenance life might ever give you.
它是唯一的寄托生活可能永远给你。
So eat up, motherfuckers!
所以吃起来，贱人！
All right, I'll start again.
好吧，我会重新开始。
[Audience groans]
[观众的呻吟]
"As long as the blade has not yet pierced this brain..."
“刀片只要还没有被刺穿这个大脑...”
♪ Take me now, baby, here as I am ♪
♪我现在，宝贝，在这里，因为我♪
♪ Pull me close, try and understand ♪
♪拉我靠近，试图了解♪
♪ Desire is hunger, is the fire I breathe ♪
♪欲望是饥饿，是火我的呼吸♪
♪ Love is the banquet on which we feed ♪
♪爱是我们喂♪宴会
Can I get through, please?
我能获得通过，好吗？
Could I get through? Let me in.
我能打通吗？让我进去。
Let me in. Let me in.
让我进去，让我进去。
I'm Nicky Gant. I produce records.
我尼基冈特。我出示记录。
You want me in your club.
你要我在你的俱乐部。
[Retches]
[干呕]
Nice.
尼斯。
I hate the bowery.
我最讨厌的包厘街。
♪ Because the night belongs to lovers ♪
♪因为晚上是属于恋人♪
♪ Because the night belongs to lust ♪
♪因为晚上属于情欲♪
♪ Because the night belongs to lovers ♪
♪因为晚上是属于恋人♪
♪ Because the night belongs to us ♪
♪因为晚上属于我们♪
♪ Have my doubts when I'm alone ♪
♪有我的怀疑，当我独自♪
♪ Love is the ring, a telephone ♪
♪爱环，电话♪
♪ Love is an angel disguised as lust ♪
♪爱是伪装成好色的天使♪
Hey, Iggy.
嘿，伊基。
Hey, Ork.
嘿，兽人。
Let's go downstairs. I'll give you head.
让我们去楼下。我会给你的头。
Why don't you just lick my stomach?
你为什么不只是舔我的肚子？
Everybody wants to suck my cock.
每个人都想要吸我的公鸡。
All right.
好的。
♪ They can't touch you now
♪你现在不能碰
♪ can't touch you now
♪ because the night belongs to lovers ♪
♪因为晚上是属于恋人♪
In you go.
在你走。
Dad, is there or isn't there a cover charge?
爸爸，或者是不是有盖费？
Someone's gotta pay.
有人得的薪酬。
Hey, John. John.
嘿，约翰，约翰。
Isn't that the guy that made that awful feedback album?
是不是那家伙，那可怕的反馈专辑吗？
John, it's Lou Reed.
约翰，这是卢·里德（Lou Reed）。
That's Lou Reed.
这是卢里德。
Oh, shit it's-- that's Lou Reed.
哦，该死的那是......  - 这是卢·里德（Lou Reed）。
We have to interview him. Yeah.
我们要采访他。嗯。
Hi, Lou.
嗨，娄。
Um, we would like to interview you
嗯，我们想采访你
for the first issue of Pun magazine.
对于第一个问题的营盘杂志。
We'd like to put you on the cover.
我们希望把你的封面上。
Cover of the first issue.
封面的第一个问题。
If you agree to do an interview.
如果你同意做一个采访。
Your circulation must be enormous.
你的血液循环必须是巨大的。
Do you like Patti Smith?
你喜欢帕蒂·史密斯吗？
Oh, yeah. Yeah, yeah.
哦，是的。啊，是啊。
What about Bruce Springsteen?
关于布鲁斯·斯普林斯廷是什么？
Oh, I love him.
哦，我爱他。
Y-you do?
Y-你怎么办？
Oh, yeah. He's one of us.
哦，是的。他是我们中的一员。
Thank you.
谢谢。
He's a shit.
他是个狗屎。
What are you talking about?
你说的是什么？
What kind of stupid question is that?
什么样的愚蠢的问题是什么？
Okay-- do I ask you what you like?
好吧 - 我问你，你喜欢什么？
Who gives a fuck what I like?
谁给他妈的我喜欢什么？
I don't even give a fuck what I like.
我什至不给他妈的，我喜欢什么。
Well, you're a rock star, man.
嗯，你是个摇滚明星，男人。
Oh, yeah. I keep forgetting.
哦，是的。我总是忘记。
Sontag called it the sensibility of failed seriousness.
桑塔格称之为失败的严重性的敏感性。
What's their name?
他们叫什么名字？
The Ramones.
雷蒙斯。
Look like they were raised under police lamps.
看起来像他们提出了根据警方灯。
[Hilly] What do you guys have for me?
[希利]你们有什么适合我吗？
We got four songs:
我们得到了四首歌曲：
I don't wanna walk around with you,
我不想走动，
I don't wanna be learned,
我不想了解，
I don't wanna be tamed,
我不想被驯服，
and I don't wanna go down to the basement.
，我不想要去到地下室。
Lot of things you don't wanna do.
很多你不想做的事情。
Yeah.
嗯。
Anything you wanna do?
你想要做什么？
We're working on something now.
我们现在正在做某件事情。
Something positive?
积极的东西吗？
Yeah. It's--it's called I wanna sniff some glue.
嗯。那是......  - 我想这就是所谓的嗅出一些胶水。
Good to have a point of view.
好有一个观点。
One, two, three, four!
一，二，三，四！
[Dischordant music]
[音乐Dischordant]
What the fuck are you playing?
你在玩什么他妈的？
Ah, fuck!
啊，他妈的！
You guys wanna try it again? Yeah.
你们想再试一次吗？嗯。
Is Johnny coming back? [Glass breaks]
是约翰尼回来了吗？ [玻璃减免]
What are we playing? Johnny!
我们玩的是什么？约翰尼！
Johnny?
约翰尼？
[Johnny] Fuck!
[约翰尼]他妈的！
Lively!
活泼！
One, two, three, four!
一，二，三，四！
♪ Sittin' in a hospital bed ♪
♪坐在医院的病床上♪
♪ Sittin' in a hospital bed
♪坐在医院的病床上
♪ sittin' in a hospital bed ♪
♪坐在医院的病床上♪
♪ I--I want life
♪我 - 我想要的生活
♪ I want my life
♪我想我的生活
♪ I got knocked down, but I'll get up ♪
♪我撞倒了，但我会起床♪
Nobody is gonna like you guys.
没人会像你这样的家伙。
But I'll have you back.
但我要你回来。
The city's going bankrupt.
城市的破产。
It's like a disease.
这就像一种疾病。
Which I would prefer not to catch.
我宁愿不要抓。
Meaning?
含义？
We have to get our affairs in order.
我们必须让我们的事务。
I'm working on it.
我的工作就可以了。
Your working isn't working, hilly.
你的工作是不工作，希利。
[Hilly] Coming to you
[希利]你来
from the bowery of New York City,
从纽约市柏威里，
Wayne county.
韦恩县。
Hello, sex kittens!
您好，性别小猫！
Eat my pussy!
吃我的猫！
Wish I had one. Oh!
希望我有一个。哦！
[Cheers, whistling]
[干杯，呼啸]
Here we go! Here we go.
在这里，我们走！在这里，我们走了。
Ready, ready, ready, ready, ready!
准备好了，准备好了，准备好了，准备好了，准备好了！
One, two, three, I'Chaim!
一，二，三，I'Chaim！
♪ Wanted nothing more
♪通缉无非
♪ I know you wouldn't go...
♪我知道你会不会去...
No, no, no, no, no!
不，不，不，不，不！
C'mere.
C'mere。
I'm Nicky Gant!
我尼基冈特！
Nicky fuckin' Gant!
尼基他妈的'的Gant！
I produce records!
我出示记录！
Hilly told me this was on the house!
希利告诉我这是在房子上！
No money.
没有钱。
We cool?
大家冷静？
♪ You were a marksman
♪你是一个神射手
♪ told me that law, like wine, is ageless ♪
♪法律告诉我，像酒，是永恒♪
You got any--any chips or something?
你有什么 - 任何芯片或东西的？
Gonna have to do something about that stage.
要去做点什么那个阶段。
Well, you might want to think about having fewer
那么，你可能要想想有较少
"guests of hilly" and more paying customers
“客人希利”和更多的付费客户
if you want to pay for it.
如果你想为它付出。
I'm with Lisa on this one.
我与莉萨在这一个。
You gotta spend money to make money.
你得花钱才能赚钱。
You gotta have money to spend money to make money.
你得有钱，花钱赚钱。
And since you spend all the money you make,
因为你花了所有的钱，你做，
you don't have any money to spend.
你不必花费任何金钱。
So you might want to think
所以，你可能要考虑
about saving the money you make
节省的钱，你做
instead of spending the money you make!
而不是花的钱，你做！
All right. We're gonna try that one again.
好的。我们要去尝试一次。
[Audience cheering]
[观众欢呼]
What are you doing?
你在做什么？
Damn it, dad.
该死的，爸爸。
What, two bankruptcies wasn't enough for you?
什么，两个破产是不够的，你呢？
Why not go for three? Stop.
为什么不走三？停止。
No, I'm taking over the finances.
不，我接手的资金。
No, you're not. You're fired.
不，你不是。你被解雇了。
You're firing me?
你要解雇我？
Yeah. Get the hell out.
嗯。滚开。
♪ I want my life
♪我想我的生活
things are not gonna work out with her.
事情是不是要去工作了她。
Everything all right, hilly?
一切都好，希利？
[Man] Hey, so, Debbie,
[文]嘿，因此，黛比，
who were the people you, you know, idolized as an artist?
谁是你的人，你知道，作为一个艺术家崇拜的偶像？
Fuck, you know, I always really liked Brigitte Bardot.
他妈的，你知道，我总是很喜欢碧姬·巴铎。
Uh-huh.
嗯。
I thought she was sort of a continental punk, you know? Yeah.
我想她是欧陆朋克，你知道吗？嗯。
I always thought sex was a cool thing to sell.
我一直以为性是一件很酷的事情，出售。
A sure thing.
一个肯定的事情。
I wish I'd invented sex.
我希望我能发明性。
You like sex?
你想做爱吗？
God, look at this!
天啊，你看这个！
I'm sick of the goddamn fleas from hilly's dog.
我生病了该死的希利的狗跳蚤。
Have you considered boots?
你有没有考虑靴？
Boots?
靴子？
♪
♪ Can I describe what it's like ♪
♪我可以形容是什么样子♪
♪ To have sex with the light on? ♪
♪有性行为的光？ ♪
♪ And would you feel right
♪你会感觉
♪ if I did you tonight and put the bite on? ♪
♪如果我这样做你今晚把咬？ ♪
♪ All this and more little girl ♪
♪所有这一切以及更多的小女孩♪
♪ How 'bout on the floor little girl? ♪
♪怎么回合在地板上的小女孩吗？ ♪
♪ Time to implore you girl
♪时间恳求你的女孩
♪ I'm just a dead boy
♪我只是一个死的男孩
♪ you know that I'm just a dead boy ♪
♪你知道，我只是一个死男孩♪
♪ I wanna be a dead boy
♪我想成为一个死了的男孩
♪ I'll die for you
♪我会为你死
♪ if you want me to
♪如果你要我
♪ got a feeling in my knees ♪
♪有一种感觉，我的膝盖♪
♪ That tell me the degrees I been loved on ♪
♪告诉我度，我被亲人♪
♪ Ya got dents in your head ♪
♪雅在你的脑袋有凹痕♪
♪ That tell me all the beds you been shoved on ♪
♪这一切都告诉我你的床猛♪
♪ All this and more little girl ♪
♪所有这一切以及更多的小女孩♪
♪ How 'bout on the floor little girl? ♪
♪怎么回合在地板上的小女孩吗？ ♪
♪ No time to implore you girl ♪
恳求你的女孩♪♪没有时间
♪ I'm just a dead boy
♪我只是一个死的男孩
♪ you know that I'm just a dead boy ♪
♪你知道，我只是一个死男孩♪
♪ I wanna be a dead boy
♪我想成为一个死了的男孩
♪ I'll die for you if you want me to ♪
♪我会为你死，如果你要我♪
♪ Look out!
♪当心！
Don't tell me. "There's something there."
不要告诉我。 “有什么东西在那里。”
There is definitely something there.
肯定是有什么东西。
The dead boys.
死去的男孩。
As long as they don't take their name too seriously.
只要他们不采取他们的名字太当回事。
Hilly Kristal.
希利克里什塔尔。
Cheetah chrome.
猎豹铬。
That was good. It was really good.
这是很好的。它真的很不错。
Thank you, sir. That means a lot, you know?
谢谢你，先生。这意味着很多，你知道吗？
Your dog is crapping on the floor, sir.
您的狗排泄的地板上，先生。
Yeah, he does that.
是啊，他这样做的。
I piss in ice machines.
我小便制冰机。
Where you guys from?
你在哪里的家伙吗？
Cleveland, sir.
克利夫兰，先生。
Well, I'm impressed with the youth of Cleveland.
好吧，我印象深刻与克利夫兰的青春。
Oh, you shouldn't be. Why not?
哦，你不应该的。为什么不呢？
Lotta losers.
洛塔失败者。
Well, you seem awfully polite.
嗯，你似乎非常有礼​​貌。
Yeah, well, we were altar boys.
是啊，我们是祭坛男孩。
That was a while ago.
这是前一段时间。
Look, Mr. Kristal, do we get the gig here or not?
看，克里什塔尔先生，​​我们这里的演出与否？
Yeah. No shit!
嗯。没有狗屎！
Holy fuck.
圣他妈的。
Spoken like a true altar boy.
说话像一个真正的祭坛男孩。
[Woman] Some say punk promotes a message of violence.
[女]有人说，朋克促进暴力的消息。
I mean, what we're doing is not really destructive, you know?
我的意思是，我们正在做的是不是真的破坏性的，你知道吗？
So it's not a statement of aggression?
因此，它不是侵略的声明？
We're just letting out a little energy and frustration.
我们只是让出一点点的能量和挫折。
And where better to do that?
更好地做到这一点呢？
Here or on the streets?
在这里或在街道上呢？
Good point. Hi, mom!
好点。嗨，妈妈！
Uh, yeah.
嗯，是啊。
It's actually really healthy.
它实际上是真正的健康。
So what kind of girls do you like?
那么什么样的女孩你喜欢吗？
All kinds.
所有种。
I like the ones that like to fuck and leave in the morning.
我喜欢那些喜欢他妈的早上离开。
Stiv, she just wants to give you a blowjob.
STIV，她只是想给你口交。
Cut.
剪下。
I dare you.
我敢说你。
You know better than to dare me.
你知道更好的比我不敢。
♪ Hot flashes burning my brain ♪
♪潮热燃烧我的大脑♪
♪ Your tongue lashes drive me insane ♪
♪你的舌头睫毛让我发疯♪
♪ From New York City to LA ♪
♪从纽约到洛杉矶的♪
♪ You're known as the hottest lay ♪
♪你被称为最热门的裁员♪
♪ And ya pink canopy gonna shackle ya down ♪
♪雅粉红色篷会卸雅跌♪
♪ You crossed every back in town ♪
♪你越过每回到镇上♪
♪ From a cherry runaway to a bowery queen ♪
♪从一个樱桃失控的一个BOWERY女王♪
♪ Used up before your sweet sixteen ♪
♪♪之前，你的甜蜜16
♪ Everyone knows you were caught ♪
♪每个人都知道你被抓♪
♪ With the meat in your mouth ♪
♪在你的嘴里的肉♪
♪ Said everyone knows
♪说大家都知道
♪ you been caught with the meat in your mouth ♪
♪你在你的嘴里的肉被抓♪
Whoo!
喔！
♪ Look for love on a one-way street ♪
♪一个单向的街道上寻找爱情♪
♪ Bedding down with every--
♪羽绒寝具与每 -
♪ a-stripping and a-dancing and a-buying some downs ♪
♪一个剥离和舞蹈和购买一些起伏♪
See? It's not all about violence!
看到了吗？这还不是全部的暴力行为！
Cut! Cut!
切！切！
Yeah, stiv!
是啊，STIV！
Gettin' his dick sucked. Oh, shit.
刚开了他的家伙吸。哦，狗屎。
Fresca.
弗雷斯卡。
On the house.
在房子上。
Stan.
斯坦。
You know I got nothing against you, right?
你知道我什么都没对你，对不对？
I like to think anyone
我喜欢认为任何人
who shares a drink in my club is my friend.
谁分享我的俱乐部喝的，是我的朋友。
Well, as your friend,
那么，作为你的朋友，
we've had some complaints.
我们已经有一些投诉。
About what?
关于什么？
Hey, hilly.
嘿，希利。
Uh, excuse me.
呃，原谅我。
Now, I'm just the messenger here, all right?
现在，我只是这里的使者，所有的权利吗？
But I understand the complaints
不过，据我所知，投诉
are about the...
是的...
Element your club attracts.
元素吸引你的俱乐部。
Are you kidding me?
你在开玩笑吧？
If anything, I'm cleaning the street up.
如果有的话，我打扫街道。
I am just the messenger here.
我只是这里的使者。
I mean, people bigger than you and I
我的意思是，人比你和我
are tugging the strings and stirring the shit.
揪着字符串和搅拌狗屎。
And I also understand
而且我也了解到
that you're three months behind on your rent.
你3个月落后于你的租金。
Now that kind of thing just doesn't help.
现在那种事只是于事无补。
Pay your bills, Kristal.
支付帐单，克里什塔尔。
Pay your fuckin' bills.
支付他妈的票据。
I don't like that guy.
我不喜欢那个家伙。
♪
♪ I got a spirit in my house
♪我的精神在我的房子
♪ and I know it ain't no... ♪
♪，我知道它是不是没有... ♪
I know you got more junk, man.
我知道你得到了更多的垃圾，男人。
Come on. Give me the fuckin' drug.
来吧。给我该死的药物。
Come on, Idaho. Give me the fuckin' drug.
来吧，爱达荷。给我该死的药物。
Not in... my club!
不...我的俱乐部！
[Idaho] Come on, hilly. Be cool, man.
[爱达荷州]来吧，希利。冷静，男人。
Like I was saying previously, Stan,
就像我以前说，斯坦，
these two gentlemen
这两位先生
were not abiding by the rigorous code of ethics
不遵守严格的道德守则
I strive to maintain in my establishment.
我努力保持我的成立。
Well, that's not very good, now, is it, boys?
嗯，这是不是很好，现在是什么，男孩？
♪ In my house, in my house ♪
♪在我的房子，我的房子♪
What are we stopping for?
什么是我们停下来？
Joey fell off the stage, John.
乔伊摔下舞台，约翰。
Fuckin' think I didn't fuckin' notice?!
他妈的觉得我做得不是他妈的'的通知？
Ah, fuck!
啊，他妈的！
♪
♪ I know a girl from a lonely street ♪
♪我知道一个女孩从一个孤独的街道♪
♪ Cold as ice cream but still as sweet ♪
♪冷的冰淇淋，但仍甜♪
♪ Dry your eyes Sunday girl ♪
♪擦干的自己的眼睛周日女孩♪
♪ Hey I saw your guy
♪嘿，我看到了你的家伙
♪ with a different girl
♪与不同的姑娘
♪ looks like he's in another world ♪
♪看起来他在另一个世界♪
♪ Run and hide Sunday girl
♪运行和隐藏周日女孩，
[feedback whines]
[反馈哼唧]
Hey, all you wannabes, I'm fuckin' Iggy pop!
嘿，你的崇拜者，我他妈的“伊基流行！
Let's play some real fuckin' music!
让我们玩一些真正该死的音乐吧！
"I wanna be your dog." Fuck you, Iggy!
“我想成为你的狗。”你他妈的，伊基！
One, two, three, four!
一，二，三，四！
♪
♪ So messed up
♪所以搞砸了
♪ I want you here
♪我希望你在这里
♪ in my room
♪在我的房间
♪ I want you here
♪我希望你在这里
♪ now we're gonna be
♪现在我们要去
♪ face to face
♪面对面
♪ and I'll lay right down
♪，我会打好降权
♪ in my favorite place
♪我最喜欢的地方
♪ now I wanna
♪现在我想
♪ be your dog
♪是你的狗
♪ now I wanna
♪现在我想
♪ be your dog
♪是你的狗
♪ now I wanna
♪现在我想
♪ be your dog
♪是你的狗
fuck the bogus claims.
他妈的假索赔。
I'm the pioneer of punk.
我是朋克的先驱。
Stage dive. I was the first.
舞台潜水。我是第一次。
See the bands are not political, but their disavowing of politics
乐队不是政治，但他们的政治disavowing的
in and of itself, it is political.
在其本身，它是政治性的。
I belong to the blank generation.
我属于空白的一代。
And relevant! And timely!
有关！及时！
John, hilly is a modern-day salonist!
约翰，希利是一个现代salonist的！
Like a drug I never did before.
像药一样，我从来没有过。
Ooh, no no no, I like that!
哦，不不不，我喜欢！
It's true, uh, yeah,
这是真的，呃，是啊，
modern-day mabel dodge, right?
现代天梅伯尔的躲闪，右？
Gertrude Stein! Yeah! Yeah!
格特鲁德·斯泰因！呀！呀！
Picasso painted gertrude Stein
毕加索的格特鲁德·斯泰因
sitting in her chair in her salon of old.
坐在椅子老在她的沙龙。
You should draw hilly
你应该画希利
sitting on his couch at CB's.
在CB的坐在他的沙发上。
The grand curator of punk!
盛大朋克馆长！
Mother always said,
母亲总是说，
"you have to listen to hear."
“你必须听听。”
50 cents, please.
50美分，请。
Thank you, Annie.
谢谢你，安妮。
You're up first tomorrow, Annie.
你明天第一，安妮。
Shirts, then Ramones,
衬衫，然后雷蒙斯
then dictators.
然后独裁者。
You scare them.
你吓唬他们。
Yeah, probably.
是啊，大概。
This place is starting to happen.
这个地方开始出现。
It's still shit-ass music,
它仍然是狗屎驴音乐，
you ask me.
你问我。
It's not the Grand Ole Opry.
这不是大奥普里。
It's hard to get Conway Twitty down to the bowery.
这是很难获得康威特威蒂柏威里。
One day.
有一天。
Maybe me and the boys'll hang back till then.
也许我和boys'll的挂到那时。
Stop scaring the kids.
不要吓唬孩子。
Let you grow this place into a, uh,
让你成长的这个地方变成一个，嗯，
something.
一些东西。
Then when you're famous, and old Twitty shows up,
然后，当你出名，老康威特威蒂显示，
I'll be back and I'm bringing all my friends.
我会回来的，我把我所有的朋友。
Admission on the house.
入场的房子。
Don't forget, we're right down the block.
不要忘了，我们是正确的跌块。
Thanks, Leslie.
谢谢你，莱斯利。
Nobody calls me that.
没有人这样叫我。
Except my grandma.
除了我奶奶。
All right, boys, let's get the hell out
所有权利，孩子们，让我们滚开
of this punk-ass excuse for a bar.
的朋克屁股酒吧的借口。
You want a re-match, you know where to find me.
你想重新比赛，你知道在哪里可以找到我。
Oh...
哦......
One more thing.
还有一件事。
Clean those fucking toilets.
清洁那些该死的厕所。
They just-- you can't--
他们只是 - 你不能 -
it's the sm--
它的SM  -
they're disgusting.
他们恶心。
Cool.
凉爽。
Fuckin' cool.
他妈的爽。
Fuckin' fuckin' cool.
该死的该死的凉爽。
Hilly!
希利！
Sire records.
外祖父记录。
This is the contract.
这是该合约。
Congratulations.
恭喜。
You pissed?
你生气了？
I'd be fucking pissed.
我他妈的生气。
You're always fucking pissed.
你总是他妈的生气。
Are you kidding me? I'm proud of you guys.
你在开玩笑吧？我是你们感到骄傲。
Can't believe we got signed.
无法相信我们得到签署。
We suck.
我们闹心。
Now you gotta make a good record.
现在，你得做出了不错的战绩。
You think we're gonna be rock stars?
你认为我们会是摇滚明星？
You already are.
你已经是。
♪
♪ All by myself
♪全部由自己
♪ all by myself
♪ like everybody else
♪像其他人一样
♪
Happy Birthday.
祝你生日快乐。
You're not gonna sing?
你不会唱歌吗？
If you wanna apologize, I accept.
如果你想道歉，我接受。
If not, then shut up.
如果没有，那么闭嘴。
Yes, ma'am.
是的，夫人。
[Phone rings]
[电话铃响]
CBGB.
CBGB。
...what time we're going on tonight.
什么时候我们要在今晚。
Zeke wants to know what time they're going on tonight.
泽科想知道他们什么时候打算在今晚。
I don't know yet.
我不知道。
Bastard won't tell me.
庶子不会告诉我。
Yep, see you tonight.
没错，晚上见。
This is good for you.
这是对你有好处。
"The Ramones are the apotheosis of punk."
“雷蒙斯是朋克的典范。”
Frank rose again.
弗兰克再次上涨。
"They are an acknowledgement of the failure of glitter."
“他们是承认失败的闪光。”
That they are.
他们是。
"Brevity is the soul of wit,
“简洁是智慧的灵魂，
"and it is right at the heart of the Ramones' music.
“它是在心脏的Ramones音乐。
They cannot be accused of dragging out a number."
不能指责他们拖出一个数字。“
You just gotta hope they don't kill each other.
你只需要希望他们不要杀了对方。
Call Leslie.
呼叫莱斯利。
Number is on the wall.
号是在墙壁上。
Hilly Kristal?
希利克里什塔尔？
My understanding is that there is a, uh,
我的理解是，有一个，嗯，
problem with the rent.
租金的问题。
And when the rent doesn't get paid, it comes to me to collect.
而当租金不支付的，到我这里来收集。
But, you see, I'm forced to double it
但是，你看，我不得不加倍
to cover my overhead.
来支付我的开销。
So now we have a compounded problem...
所以现在我们有一个复合的问题...
How many are there? Three.
有多少？三。
They packin'? Yeah.
他们packin'？嗯。
The rent check's on its way,
租金支票的方式，
but I'll just...
但我只是...
Need to think about the doubling part.
需要想想倍增部分。
There's nothing to think about, Mr. Kristal.
什么都不去想，克里什塔尔先生。
You guys thirsty? Cut the shit!
你们渴了吗？切狗屎！
You have a strong business that operates
你有一个强大的业务经营
to full capacity almost every night.
满负荷几乎每天晚上。
So let me explain something to you.
因此，让我解释给你的东西。
I'm not a very patient man.
我不是一个非常有耐心的人。
So I suggest you give me what I came here for.
所以，我建议你给我什么，我来到这里。
How you been, Leslie?
你怎么样，莱斯利？
I haven't been feeling so good.
我没有感觉这么好。
Think I got a tapeworm.
觉得我有绦虫。
Quit calling me that.
叫我说，退出。
Do you guys know who you're dealing with?
你们知道你是谁处理？
Get in the fucking car!
获取该死车！
Go, let's go! Scooch over.
走，咱们走吧！挤一挤了过来。
What was that?! A shakedown.
那是什么？ A勒索。
New York style.
纽约风格。
I don't understand.
我听不懂。
You paid the rent, right?
你付房租，对不对？
Everything all right?
一切都好吗？
Why wouldn't it be?
为什么不能呢？
I wrote a rent check last week.
上周我写了一个租金检查。
So it was a misunderstanding?
所以这是一种误解？
Well, I didn't send it.
好吧，我没送。
What?!
什么？
Why not?! I forgot.
为什么不呢？我忘了。
Dad! What?
爸爸！什么？
I am taking over the books whether you like it or not!
我接管，不管你喜欢还是不喜欢的书！
Because if I don't, someone is going
因为如果我不，有人是怎么回事
to come here and kill you!
到这里来杀了你！
Okay. Okay?
好吧。好吗？
Yeah.
嗯。
Okay.
好吧。
Hello there!
你好！
Kristal, this your truck?
蕊妮，这是你的车吗？
You know it is.
你知道它是。
I'm gonna have to write you up.
我要去给你写。
Why? Did you read the sign?
为什么呢？你读的标志吗？
You and I both know
你和我都知道
how long this truck has been parked here
多久，这车已经停在这里
in this exact spot
在这个确切位置
without getting a ticket.
没有获得一票。
Well, New York is going bankrupt.
那么，纽约破产。
There's pressure to bring in some revenue.
有压力带来一些收入。
Well,
好吧，
this car has been here all day.
这款车一直在这里一整天。
Move the truck.
移动的卡车。
City's cracking down.
市打击。
You're not telling me the whole story.
你不告诉我整个故事。
What's that supposed to mean?
应该意味着什么？
Where does the cash go at the end of the night?
现金哪里去年底的夜晚吗？
After I count it?
之后，我算什么呢？
Stop it. What?
停止它。什么？
What happens to the cash at the end of the night?
会发生什么事的现金，在晚上结束的呢？
I put it in the freezer.
我把它放在冰柜。
What?
什么？
In my apartment. You got an apartment?
在我的公寓。你得到了一个公寓吗？
I can't sleep on a mattress
我不能睡在床垫
when bands are getting signed right and left.
乐队时签署右和左。
'Kay, I'm going to go through all this paper.
“凯，我将要经历这一切纸张。
And then we will know where we're at.
然后我们会知道我们在哪里。
Terrific. You go to the freezer
太棒了。转至冷藏室
in your apartment and get the money now.
在你的公寓，现在拿到了钱。
Pay the rent, now,
付房租，现在，
and take the rest to the bank, now.
其余的银行，现在。
I don't know how this is going to work out with you
我不知道这是怎么跟你去上班了
ordering me around.
订购我身边。
I don't know how it's gonna work out if I don't.
我不知道它是如何要去工作了，如果我不。
[Rock music]
[摇滚音乐]
♪
Hilly!
希利！
Damn it, hilly!
该死，希利！
Ah, shit! Goddamn it!
啊，狗屎！该死！
Turn the water off!
关闭水关！
There's water everywhere, man!
到处都是水，伙计！
Jesus Christ! Okay.
耶稣基督！好吧。
You know, Bert, I've been thinking
伯特，你知道吗，我一直在思考
I should start managing some of those bands.
我应该开始管理一些乐队。
And Jonathan shit in the front room here!
乔纳森在前面的房间在这里拉屎！
The dead boys. Talking heads.
死去的男孩。名嘴。
The shirts.
衬衫。
Punk isn't about decay,
朋克是不是衰减，
it's about the apocalypse. It's about annihilation.
它的启示。它是关于毁灭。
Nothing works, so let's skip right to armageddon.
实在不行，所以让我们跳过世界末日的权利。
If the world is ending,
如果世界结束，
you might as well do away with pretense
你还不如做幌子
and say what you think.
说出你的想法。
Uncensored sex!
未经审查的性别！
And drugs!
和毒品！
And violence!
和暴力！
Just everything.
只是一切。
Decadent sounds great right now,
颓废的声音很大，
compared to what's happening in the real world.
而在现实世界中发生的事情。
Yeah!
呀！
♪ I don't need anyone
♪我不需要任何人
♪ don't need no mom and dad ♪
♪不需要任何的妈妈和爸爸♪
Come on, Genya, they're charming!
来吧，Genya，他们是迷人！
Hilly, they're punk, and they're charming?
希利，他们是朋克，他们很迷人吗？
♪ I got some news for you
♪我一些你的消息
I want you to produce them, I think they're special.
我希望你能生产它们，我觉得他们是特殊的。
♪ I got my devil machine
♪我得到了我的魔鬼机
♪ got my electronic dream
♪得到了我的电子梦想
♪ sonic reducer, ain't no loser ♪
♪声波减速，是不是没有失败者♪
♪ Sonic reducer, ain't no loser ♪
I've been waiting for you in the office!
在办公室里，我一直在等着你！
In a minute, Lisa.
在一分钟内，丽莎。
♪ People out on the streets
♪人们在街道上
♪ they don't know who I am
♪他们不知道我是谁
♪ I watch them from my room
♪看着他们从我的房间
Mrs. Kristal!
夫人克里什塔尔！
Oh, Merv!
哦，梅尔夫！
So good to see you!
所以很高兴见到你！
Mother, welcome to CBGB.
母亲，欢迎CBGB。
Hillel.
希勒尔。
Uh, listen, I need a drink.
恩，听着，我需要喝一杯。
On the house!
房子！
Glenlivet with a twist.
与扭曲格伦利威。
Coming right up. Okay.
马上就来。好吧。
We don't have any glenlivet.
我们没有任何格伦利威。
We'll take care of it, go talk to Lisa.
我们会照顾它，去丽莎交谈。
Come this way, Mrs. Kristal.
这种方式来，克里什塔尔夫人。
I have a special spot for you right over here.
你在这里，我有一个特别的地点。
Excuse me! Watch your backs!
对不起！观看你的背影！
This is what you're spending.
这是你花什么。
This is what you're making.
这是你正在做什么。
I have to get back out there.
我从这里走出去。
Give her a minute, hilly.
给她一分钟，希利。
You're spending too much.
你花费太多。
You cannot afford to personally take on a band.
您不能亲自带。
I agree with Lisa on this.
在此，我同意与丽莎。
Oh, this is about the dead boys.
哦，这是关于死的男孩。
Ye-- before we branch out,
叶 - 之前，我们分公司，
we need to get our primary business in order.
我们需要得到我们的主要业务。
And we need to put proper vendor agreements in place.
我们需要把合适的供应商协议。
We need to have billing cycles.
我们需要有结算周期。
Look here, okay?
看看这里，好吗？
This is what you're spending on toilet paper.
这就是你花的卫生纸上。
I don't believe that.
我不相信这一点。
You're getting it from the deli, a lot of it!
你得到它从熟食店，不少呢！
If you buy it in bulk, you can get it for a fraction of the price.
如果你买散装的，你可以得到它的价格的一小部分。
This is what you're spending on beer.
这就是你对啤酒的消费。
This is what you are bringing in on the bar in general.
这就是你所带来的酒吧一般。
Hey, too many customers are drinking for free!
哎，太多的客户免费喝！
This is bullshit. Hilly, cut it out!
这是胡扯。希利，别说了！
Why are we talking about toilet paper?!
为什么我们要谈论的卫生纸？
I have Genya Ravan out there
我有Genya拉万有
ready to produce the dead boys album!
准备死男孩的专辑！
You're wasting my time!
你在浪费我的时间！
Fine.
精细。
Goddamn it, hilly.
该死，希利。
This is quite good!
这是相当不错的！
Hilly's chili, huh?
希利的辣椒，是吧？
Word is, Stiv Bators
Word是，STIV Bators
jerks off in that chili.
抽搐，辣椒。
I've had worse in my mouth.
我已经在我的嘴里差。
Everything okay, mother?
一切都还好吗，妈妈？
Delicious!
好吃！
What are you doing?
你在做什么？
Trying to light a cigarette.
试图点燃一支香烟。
You shouldn't smoke.
你不应该抽烟。
That shit'll kill ya.
这shit'll杀了你。
I don't smoke.
我不抽烟。
You know, your old man
你知道吗，你的老伙计
is really not such a bad guy.
是真的不这么一个坏家伙。
Well, you obviously don't know him very well.
好了，你显然不知道他很好。
Oh God, zip, Idaho! Please!
哦，上帝，拉链，爱达荷州！求你了！
Excuse me.
对不起。
Sometimes you hurt
有时你伤
the ones you love the most.
你爱的人最多。
What fortune cookie did you read that in?
你读了什么幸运曲奇？
Nah.
罗。
I got it from a poster in the subway
我是从一个在地铁海报
across from this bench I kinda like.
从这个板凳对面，我还挺喜欢的。
I prefer rachmaninoff, hillel.
我更喜欢拉赫玛尼诺夫，HILLEL。
Yeah, I prefer Beethoven myself.
是啊，我喜欢贝多芬自己。
That punk rock shit gives me a headache.
，朋克摇滚狗屎让我头疼。
No shit.
没有狗屎。
Mom was right to leave you.
妈妈离开你是正确的。
You're an asshole.
你是个混蛋。
Lisa what?
丽莎是什么？
In my capacity as asshole,
在我能力混蛋，
I am promoting you to vice president of business affairs.
我促进你的业务事务的副总裁。
Is that supposed to be some kind of apology?
是，应该是某种形式的道歉吗？
The dead boys are gonna change things for me, Lisa.
死去的男孩要去改变的事情对我来说，丽莎。
I am gonna get them a record deal,
我要去让他们创纪录的交易，
and they are gonna be big!
他们会大！
♪ I'm so sick of TV
♪我生病电视
♪ you know I'm getting bored of the tubes ♪
♪你知道我感到厌烦的管子♪
♪ And I'm so sick of romance ♪
♪我生病的浪漫♪
I refuse to chase you, Lisa!
我不追你，丽莎！
I've had it, hilly.
我受够了，希利。
I can't take it anymore! The fleas and the shit!
我不能把它了！跳蚤和狗屎！
Your dog is crapping everywhere!
你的狗到处拉屎！
It's disgusting, this is not a kennel!
这是令人厌恶的，这是不是一个狗窝！
Either Jonathan goes, or I go!
要么乔纳森去，还是我去吧！
Taxi, you don't like it,
出租车，你不喜欢它，
you don't have to work here!
你不必在这里工作！
♪ I don't play my stereo too ♪
♪我没有发挥出自己的立体声♪
♪ Just wanna get out on the street fights ♪
♪只是想在大街上打架♪
♪ Just ain't nothin' to do
♪只是没什么做
♪ I get on out of here
♪我离开这里
♪ find somethin' to do
♪找到事端做
♪ yeah get on out of here
♪耶离开这里
♪ just ain't nothin' to do
♪只是没什么做
so, is that your real hair color,
所以，那是你真正的发色，
or do you just dye it that way?
或者你只是染这样的吗？
Who wants to know?
谁想要知道吗？
Me.
我。
It's real.
它是真实的。
So, now you know.
所以，现在你知道了。
Yeah, we're good.
是啊，我们是很好的。
So, they vomit, they drop trow,
所以，他们呕吐，他们放弃特罗，
they slash themselves, they bleed,
他们大幅削减自己，他们流血，
they hang themselves, and that's just on stage.
他们上吊，这是刚刚在舞台上。
I think their on-stage antics
我觉得他们在舞台上的滑稽动作
are evidence of commitment.
承诺的证据。
Hilly, I don't want to produce
希利，我不想产生
a shit album for a flash-in-the-pan band.
闪光灯在泛带一个狗屎专辑。
Fine, I'll find somebody else.
好吧，我会找别人。
We're gonna need money. Yep.
我们会需要钱。没错。
And we're gonna need to take them out on the road.
我们会需要带他们出去的道路上。
Yep.
没错。
Cheetah doesn't trust me.
猎豹不信任我。
Cheetah takes too many drugs.
猎豹需要太多的药物。
Sire is interested in signing you if we
外祖父是有兴趣签下你，如果我们
can show the band is reliable
乐队是可靠的，可以显示
and people will pay to see you.
人会花钱看你。
We are the definition of reliable.
我们是可靠的定义。
What'd I miss?
我怎么会错过？
Let's make a demo and get out on the road.
让我们做一个演示走出的道路上。
Hilly, how much money is this?
希利，这是多少钱？
We are gonna rock and shock.
我们要摇滚和冲击。
Don't screw this up.
不要搞砸了。
Scouts honor.
童子军的荣誉。
Yeah, I heard she fucked bowie
是啊，我听说她性交鲍伊
at... at CB's.
在...在CB的。
In the bathroom.
在浴室里。
Fuck in a bathroom at CB's, that's not sanitary.
他妈的在浴室CB，这不是卫生。
What the fuck is that?
他妈的是什么？
What?
什么？
Get rid of those fucking things.
摆脱那些该死的东西。
They're just stickers.
他们只是贴纸。
Hilly, your manager-- hey!
希利，你的经理 - 嘿！
Hilly, your manager,
希利，你的经理，
the guy who is footing the bill
的家伙是谁买单
for all of this, he's Jewish.
对于这一切，他是犹太人。
Me, your producer, I'm Jewish.
我，你的制片人，我是犹太人。
And the guy who owns this studio,
谁拥有这个工作室的家伙，
who is doing us a favor
是谁做我们一个忙
by letting us record at these ridiculous prices,
让我们记录这些荒谬的价格，
he's got numbers tattooed on his arm.
他得到了他的手臂上纹身的数字。
Do you know what that means?
你知道这意味着什么吗？
Not really.
真的没有。
Auschwitz!
奥斯威辛集中营！
Hitler! Nazis!
希特勒！纳粹！
Now get rid of the fucking swastikas!
摆脱他妈的党徽！
Okay, fucking lighten up.
好吧，他妈的减仓。
I'll get rid of them.
我会摆脱他们。
Look, you guys, you're not Nazis, okay?
你看，你们这些家伙，你是不是纳粹，好吗？
You're punks.
你的小混混。
And anything bad, anything wrong,
什么坏事，做错什么，
you wanna do it. I get it.
你想做到这一点。我得到它。
Now let's go have a bagel.
现在，让我们有一个面包圈。
What's a bagel? What's-- what's a bagel?
一个面包圈是什么？的消闲节目 - 什么是一个面包圈？
What part of Cleveland are you from?
你是从什么克利夫兰吗？
Cleveland, Germany?
克利夫兰，德国？
[Hilly] What is punk rock?
[希利]朋克摇滚是什么？
Well, call it street music.
嗯，街头音乐。
Look, all I care about is originality.
你看，我所关心的是独具匠心。
These kids have something to say.
这些孩子有话要说。
We really should listen.
我们真的应该听。
We're the dead boys!
我们死去的男孩！
♪ I-- I don't want you
♪我 - 我不想你
♪ to hang around
♪流连
♪ yeah, I don't need you
♪是啊，我不需要你
♪ to drag me down
♪我拖
♪ I-- I don't really
♪我 - 我真的不
♪ wanna dance
♪想跳舞
hello, Poughkeepsie!
你好，波基普西！
♪ I just wanna get in your pants ♪
♪我只是想在你的裤子♪
What's up, Cleveland?
什么，克利夫兰？
Fuck you, new haven!
你他妈的，新的避风港！
Fuck off, Boston!
他妈的，波士顿！
Suck my balls, bridgeport!
吸我的球，布里奇波特！
♪ You cry and cry
♪你哭，哭
♪ you know I'll prick you in the end ♪
♪你知道我刺你到底♪
♪ Ya look at me that way, bitch ♪
♪雅看着我说，婊子♪
♪ Your face is gonna get a punch ♪
♪你的脸是会得到一拳打♪
Hello, white plains!
您好，白平原！
We're the dead boys!
我们死去的男孩！
I swallowed my gum.
我吞下的口香糖。
What the h--
什么小时 -
I mean-- what the h--
我的意思是 - 小时 -
do you want a record deal?!
你想创纪录的交易吗？
Said sorry, you know?
说了声对不起，你知道吗？
Go!
去！
Have a nice day.
有一个愉快的一天。
May I help you?
我可以帮你吗？
Why would you save
为什么你会救
for your dreams?
为你的梦想？
Why not live your dreams?
为什么不住你的梦想？
Absolutely.
当然可以。
Hilly Kristal.
希利克里什塔尔。
How much do I have in my account?
多少钱，我有我的账户？
$312.17.
312.17美元。
Keep the 17 cents.
保持的17美分。
I'll take the rest.
我会好好休息。
What are you doing, hilly?
你在做什么，希利？
Were you following me? Me?
你跟着我？我呢？
Follow you, no, why would I follow you?
跟着你，不，我为什么要跟着你吗？
Yes, I'm following you!
是的，我跟着你！
What are you doing?
你在做什么？
Investing.
投资。
In what? Treasury bills?
在哪？国库券？
I'm taking the money out of the CBGB account
我接过钱CBGB帐户
to float the dead boys development fund.
浮动死男孩发展基金。
That's the stupidest thing I've ever heard.
这是我听过的最愚蠢的事情。
You can't. You watch me.
你不能。你看我。
We got bills to pay!
我们有账单要付！
You have no vision, Merv.
你有没有眼光的Merv。
Well, I quit!
好吧，我不干了！
I'll call you later! I won't answer!
稍后我会打电话给你！我不会回答！
Oh, yes you will! No, I won't!
哦，是的，你会！不，我不会！
I went to a pawnshop.
我去了当铺。
Sold everything.
什么都卖。
My father's watch.
我父亲的手表。
They destroyed your truck.
他们毁坏了你的车。
And their equipment.
而且他们的设备。
They're gonna need equipment.
他们会需要的设备。
Why are you doing this? I believe in them.
你为什么这样做？我相信他们。
Hey.
嘿。
Thank you.
谢谢。
Why are you thanking me?
你为什么要感谢我？
Somebody should.
应该有人。
This is not the end of the world.
这不是世界末日。
I mean, this could be good for us if we manage it right.
我的意思是，如果我们管理的是正确的，这可能是对我们有好处的。
We are punks, after all.
我们是小混混，毕竟。
Blitz might be dead.
闪电可能是死了。
The last thing I care about is publicity for a band
最后一件事，我关心的是一个乐队的宣传
who's about to cost me my club.
谁是我的俱乐部。
How is he?
他怎么样？
He's, um-- he's critical.
他，嗯 - 他是关键。
Fuck.
他妈的。
Do you still have the money?
你还有钱吗？
Yeah.
嗯。
Blitz is gonna need it.
闪电会需要它。
Make sure he gets good medical care.
确保他得到良好的医疗照顾。
Where you going?
你要去哪里？
I'm not your father!
我不是你的父亲！
I'm just your manager.
我只是你的经理。
I can't do this anymore.
我不能再这样下去了。
[The Velvet Underground's oh! Sweet nuthin']
[地下丝绒的哦！甜废柴']
♪
Jersey.
新泽西州。
Hightstown.
海茨敦。
♪ Say a word for Jimmy brown
♪吉米 - 布朗说一个字
♪ he ain't got nothin' at all ♪
♪自己是不是得了什么的♪
♪ Not the shirt right off his back ♪
♪♪脱下他的衬衫权
♪ He ain't got nothin' at all ♪
♪他是不是得了什么的♪
♪ And say a word for ginger brown ♪
♪说一个字姜棕♪
♪ Walks with his head down to the ground ♪
♪走与他的头倒在地上♪
♪ Took the shoes
♪拿着鞋子
♪ right off his feet
他的脚♪右
♪ threw the poor boy right out in the street ♪
♪把可怜的孩子在街上♪
♪ And this is what he said
♪这是什么，他说
♪ oh sweet nothing...
♪甜哦什么...
Can I help you?
我可以帮你吗？
I'm sorry.
对不起。
I grew up here.
我在这里长大。
Uh-huh.
嗯。
Hilly Kristal.
希利克里什塔尔。
Hilly.
希利。
Are you the kid that started that rock 'n roll club?
你的孩子开始，摇滚乐俱乐部？
Unfortunately, that's me.
不幸的是，那就是我。
My nephew's band played there once.
有一次我侄子的乐队演奏。
Teenage Jesus and the jerks.
十几岁的耶稣和抽搐。
Coffee's inside, come on.
咖啡的里面，来吧。
♪ I saw a little bird
♪我看见一只小鸟
♪ sitting in a tree
♪坐在一棵大树
♪ who wanted to start a family ♪
♪谁想要开始一个家庭♪
♪ He went tweet, tweet, tweet tweet ♪
♪他去鸣叫，鸣叫，鸣叫鸣叫♪
♪ He were looking for a she ♪
♪他看着她♪
♪ He couldn't wait to find a mate ♪
♪他迫不及待地找到一个伴侣♪
♪ Sat in a tree and sang a plea ♪
♪周六在一棵树上唱认罪♪
♪ He went tweet, tweet, tweet tweet ♪
♪他去鸣叫，鸣叫，鸣叫鸣叫♪
♪ He were looking for a she ♪
♪他看着她♪
Where the hell are you?!
你到底是在哪里？
Everybody is worried about you!
每个人都为你担心！
I'm done. It's over.
我完成了。它结束了。
No, no way. I won't let you.
没有，没有办法。我不会放过你的。
I can't even pay the rent.
我什至不能支付租金。
Yeah, you can.
是的，你可以。
And yes, you will.
是的，你会的。
Look, you may be a lousy businessman, dad,
你看，你可能是一个糟糕的商人，爸爸，
but, damn it, you are the father of underground rock
但是，该死的，你是地下岩石的父亲
and OMFUG, whatever the hell that is.
OMFUG，无论地狱。
And it's not all about you.
它不是关于你的一切。
Okay, there are kids out there in bands
好吧，有孩子在那里乐队
or forming bands hoping to play at CBGB one day.
或形成乐队希望能起到CBGB一天。
So stop feeling sorry for yourself right now and get over here.
所以，不要感觉对不起自己的权利，并在这里获得。
Lisa, stop shouting and feed Jonathan.
丽莎，停止喊，并养活乔纳森。
[Phone rings]
[电话铃响]
CBGB.
CBGB。
No. I don't have the lineup for tonight.
我没有为今晚的阵容。
[Man] All right.
[文]所有权利。
[Phone rings]
[电话铃响]
CBGB.
CBGB。
Hey, hilly!
嘿，希利！
Hilly.
希利。
I just don't get it.
我只是不明白这一点。
Why did you risk everything on the dead boys?
你为什么就死了男孩的一切风险？
Was it the auto-asphyxiation or the self-mutilation?
自动窒息或自残吗？
They could've been a bellwether.
他们可以一直的领头羊。
That's debatable.
这是值得商榷的。
I'm going to law school.
我去了法学院。
Really?
真的吗？
How come?
怎么来的？
Cause I know you're gonna need me to.
因为我知道你会需要我。
Even though I know you'll never admit it.
即使我知道你永远不会承认这一点。
Your friends have been waiting out there for you all fucking day.
你的朋友们一直在等待有你所有该死的一天。
Get your ass out there!
给我滚出来！
I really don't appreciate all the swearing.
我真的不喜欢所有的脏话。
Um...
嗯......
I know you all counted on me, but the thing is, I'm broke,
我知道你们都算在我身上，但事情是，我打破了，
and I think we're gonna have to close the club.
我觉得我们得关闭俱乐部。
Oh, God!
哦，上帝！
How many years have we listened to your shit?
多少年了，我们听你的屎？
Lisa and I made a few calls.
丽莎和我打了几个电话。
A lot of calls.
很多电话。
And people wanted to help.
人们想提供帮助。
Yeah, like people that you helped
是啊，喜欢的人，你帮
even when you didn't have the money.
甚至当你没有足够的钱。
But, uh...
但是，呃......
Lisa's gonna take care of this.
丽莎是会好好照顾。
She's gonna pay the bills.
她会支付账单。
She's gonna get the place back on track.
她要去的地方，回到正轨。
I want you to have this.
我希望你能有这样的。
It's all I got.
这是我的一切。
I have--I have a-- I have a...
我 - 我有一个 - 我有一个...
Don't tell anybody.
不要告诉任何人。
I have a gold filling in my tooth, in the back.
我有一个金填我的牙齿，在后面。
You could probably take it out like this.
这样，你也许可以把它拿出来。
Thanks, Idaho.
谢谢，爱达荷。
Looks like I'm not gonna need either of those.
看起来像我不会需要的那些。
Okay.
好吧。
When you're ready.
当你准备好。
Thank you, sir. It's an honor to be here.
谢谢你，先生。这是一个荣幸来到这里。
You play too loud, I'm walking out.
你玩太大，我走了。
All right, guys. Anytime.
好吧，伙计们。祝你好运。
♪
♪ Roxanne
♪罗克珊
♪ you don't have to put on the red light ♪
♪你不必把红灯♪
♪ Those days are over
♪那些日子已经一去不复返了
♪ you don't have to sell your body to the night ♪
♪你不卖你的身体到了夜晚♪
♪ Roxanne
♪罗克珊
♪ you don't have to wear that dress tonight ♪
♪你不必今晚穿的那件衣服♪
♪ Walk the streets for money
♪步行街上的钱
♪ you don't care if it's wrong or if it's right ♪
♪你不在乎，如果它是错的，或者如果它是正确的♪
Well, there is something there.
嗯，有那么点意思。
♪ You don't have to put on the red light ♪
♪你不必把红灯♪
♪ Roxanne...
♪罗克珊...
There is definitely something there.
肯定是有什么东西。
♪ Roxanne
♪罗克珊
♪ put on the red light
♪把红灯
♪ Roxanne
♪罗克珊
♪ put on the red light
♪把红灯
♪ Roxanne
♪罗克珊
♪ put on the red light
♪把红灯
♪ Roxanne
♪罗克珊
♪ put on the red light
♪把红灯
♪ Roxanne
♪罗克珊
♪ put on the red light
♪把红灯
I opened...
我打开...
CBGB because...
CBGB，因为......
I thought country music was gonna become the next big thing.
我想，乡村音乐是会成为下一个大的事情。
And it did.
它做到了。
In Nashville.
在纳什维尔。
♪ Know my mind is made up
♪知道我已经下定决心了
♪ so put away your makeup
♪所以收起你的化妆
♪ told you once, I won't tell you again ♪
♪告诉你一次，我不会告诉你再次♪
♪ It's a bad way
♪这是一个糟糕的方​​式
[talking heads' life during wartime]
[战时谈论元首的生活]
♪
♪ Heard of a van
♪听说一辆面包车
♪ it's loaded with weapons
♪装有武器
♪ packed up and ready to go ♪
♪收拾行装，准备去♪
♪ Heard of some grave sites
♪听说一些墓地
♪ out by the highway
♪由高速公路
♪ a place where nobody knows ♪
♪没有人知道的地方♪
♪ The sound of gunfire
♪枪声
♪ off in the distance
♪在距离
♪ I'm getting used to it now ♪
♪我习惯现在♪
♪ Lived in a brownstone
♪住在赤褐色砂石建筑
♪ lived in a ghetto
♪住在贫民窟
♪ I've lived all over this town ♪
♪我住在这个小镇♪
♪ This ain't no party
♪这不是任何一方
♪ this ain't no disco
♪这不是没有迪斯科
♪ this ain't no fooling around ♪
♪♪左右，这不是没有嘴硬
♪ No time for dancing
♪没有时间跳舞
♪ or lovey dovey
♪或lovey多维
♪ I ain't got time for that now ♪
♪我是不是得了时间，现在♪
♪ Transmit the message
♪发送消息
♪ to the receiver
♪到接收器
♪ hope for an answer some day ♪
♪希望有一天答案♪
♪ I got three passports
♪我得到了三个护照
♪ a couple of visas
♪一对夫妇签证
♪ you don't even know my real name ♪
♪你甚至不知道我的真实姓名♪
♪ High on a hillside
♪高的一个山坡上
♪ the trucks are loading
♪卡车装载
♪ everything's ready to roll
♪一切都已经准备好了
♪ I sleep in the daytime
♪我在白天睡觉
♪ I work in the nighttime
♪我的工作在夜间
♪ I might not ever get home
♪我可能不会回家
♪ this ain't no party
♪这不是任何一方
♪ this ain't no disco
♪这不是没有迪斯科
♪ this ain't no fooling around ♪
♪♪左右，这不是没有嘴硬
♪ This ain't no mudd club
♪这不是没有穆德俱乐部
♪ or CBGB
♪或CBGB
♪ I ain't got time for that now ♪
♪我是不是得了时间，现在♪
Talking heads, get the hell up here please.
名嘴，在这里得到了地狱。
We wanna start by thanking hilly Kristal.
我们要开始感谢希利克里什塔尔的。
We'd to invite hilly up here.
我们会邀请希利这里。
Hilly is the reason that we're here,
希利的是，我们在这里的原因，
that the Ramones are here,
雷蒙斯都在这里，
that blondie are here.
金发在这里。
He kept us alive.
他让我们活着。
He fed us and he supported us
他喂养我们，他支持我们
in every way possible.
在一切可能的方式。
He told us we needed to expand our sound,
他告诉我们，我们需要扩大我们的声音，
and he taught us a lot about ethics,
他教了我们很多关于道德，
about how to treat people.
如何对待人。
I'd like to thank hilly again.
我想再次感谢希利。
When we were starting out,
当我们开始了，
there really weren't clubs
果真有没有俱乐部
where bands could play their own material,
乐队可以发挥自己的材料，
and, uh, poor hilly wanted
，嗯，可怜的希利通缉
to have a bluegrass bar on the bowery,
柏威里有一个兰草酒吧，
and to have some other music as well.
并有一些其他的音乐。
I guess the road didn't go that way.
我猜路上没走那条路。
The road took another turn.
的道路又反过来。
And, uh, thanks to--
，嗯，感谢 -
I mean, we thank him,
我的意思是，我们感谢他，
because he went that direction and didn't mind.
因为他那个方向去，并不介意。
It was just extraordinary,
这是刚非凡，
the fact that bands came out of the woodwork.
事实上，带出来的木工。
They were everywhere.
他们无处不在。
They were coming from out of state.
他们来自外州。
Nobody knew they were there.
没有人知道他们在那里。
They came out because there was somewhere to play.
他们出来，因为有地方玩。
Hilly brought the music into existence in many ways.
希利带来的音乐，在许多方面存在。
[Applause]
[鼓掌]
♪
♪ I saw a little bird
♪我看见一只小鸟
♪ sittin' in a tree
♪坐在一棵树
♪ who wanted to start a family ♪
♪谁想要开始一个家庭♪
♪ Who went tweet, tweet
♪谁去鸣叫，鸣叫
♪ tweet, tweet
♪鸣叫，鸣叫
♪ he went lookin' for a she ♪
♪他去看着她♪
♪ He couldn't wait to find a mate ♪
♪他迫不及待地找到一个伴侣♪
♪ Sat in a tree and sang a plea ♪
♪周六在一棵树上唱认罪♪
♪ He went tweet, tweet
♪他去鸣叫，鸣叫
♪ tweet, tweet
♪鸣叫，鸣叫
♪ he went looking for a she ♪
♪他去寻找她♪
♪ There was a little bee
♪有一只小蜜蜂
♪ a-feelin' mighty free
♪一个感觉威武免费
♪ some honey, he said is good for me ♪
♪一些蜂蜜，他说是为我好♪
♪ He went a-buzz, buzz
♪他走了声，嗡嗡声
♪ a-buzz, buzz
♪一个声，嗡嗡声
♪ he went looking for a she
♪他去寻找一个她
♪ you love me, I love you ♪
♪你爱我，我爱你♪
♪ Let's both do what the birds and bees do ♪
♪让我们都做了什么鸟儿和蜜蜂做♪
♪ Buzz, buzz, buzz
♪嗡嗡声，嗡嗡声，嗡嗡声
♪ tweet, tweet, tweet
♪鸣叫，鸣叫，鸣叫
♪ that means I love you, love you, love you ♪
♪这意味着我爱你，爱你，爱你♪
♪ I love you all the time
♪我爱你所有的时间
♪ isn't it a pity that the lady from the city ♪
♪是不是很可惜，夫人从城市♪
♪ Went inside a pen and was taken for a hen ♪
♪里面去了一支钢笔和一个母鸡♪
♪ Turned her back on a rooster ♪
♪转过身去背对着一只公鸡♪
♪ And when he promptly goosed her ♪
♪以及当，他及时goosed她♪
♪ She received such a bruise to her ♪
♪她收到这样的挫伤她的♪
♪ More than she was used to
♪比她更被用来
♪ that she went back to the city ♪
♪，她回城去了♪
♪ And never came here again
♪从来没有再次来到这里
♪ isn't that a pity
♪不可惜
♪ that means I love you, love you, love you ♪
♪这意味着我爱你，爱你，爱你♪
♪ I love you all the time
♪我爱你所有的时间
♪ that means I love you, love you, love you, love you ♪
♪这意味着我爱你，爱你，爱你，爱你♪
♪ All the time
♪所有的时间
♪ that means I love you, love you, love you ♪
♪这意味着我爱你，爱你，爱你♪
♪ I love you all the time
♪我爱你所有的时间